fictionwise.com 2013-04-05

# Fictionwise eBooks: Free eBooks, eBooks for your iPhone, BlackBerry, Android device, Symbian Mobile Phone, Windows Mobile Smartphone, Palm handheld, PC, Mac and more!

**Privacy Statement for Fictionwise** Fictionwise, Inc. has created this privacy statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the website **http://www.fictionwise.com**. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information. 

Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart, to make login more convenient (auto-login), and for other user benefits (e.g., turn popup ads off for frequent visitors). 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (such as name and email address). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

This site contains links to other sites. **Fictionwise** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. Contact information from the order form is used to send orders and information about our company to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

We may use both "open-tracking" and "click-tracking" in our HTML newsletters (i.e. emails that contain text and images). Open-tracking allows us to find out how many people have viewed our email newsletters and click-tracking allows us to find out which links in the newsletter were clicked on. This helps us to refine and improve the editorial content of our newsletters, and to provide you with relevant information. 

"HTML-sensing" may be used to determine if your email client supports HTML-based emails. This is employed only if you request our system to detect whether you can receive HTML emails. 

Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (such as email address) and their opinions on stories they read. We use contact data from our surveys to send the user information about our company and/or to recommend stories we feel they may enjoy reading. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (such as email address). We use contact data from our contests to send users information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Note: If Fictionwise is bought or purchased by another company or individual, member information would be an asset and part of such a sale. 

## Public Forums

This site may have chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

## Overall

Fictionwise does not sell or share personal information about its users to any third parties. Fictionwise may release general information, such as website traffic statistics, but never any information that would allow the third party to contact a Fictionwise user. 

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

## Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. Web based option: click here. 
  2. You can send mail to the following postal address: 

**Fictionwise  
346 Main St.  
Chatham, NJ 07928**

## Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

To change personal information in your profile, Login at Fictionwise.com, go to your Bookshelf, Click on "Update My Profile" and change any information that you wish, including opting in or out of receiving Fictionwise newsletters. To cancel your account, email [support@fictionwise.com](mailto:support@fictionwise.com) FROM THE SAME EMAIL ADDRESS in your profile (that allows us to verify who you are). 

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or Fictionwise, please contact: 

**Scott Pendergrast  
Fictionwise   
346 Main St.  
Chatham, NJ 07928  
support@fictionwise.com**

Fictionwise reserves the right to change or update these terms.
